fitschigogerl.com 2016-02-16

# Fitschigogerl AG

Privacy Policy Statement of Fitschigogerl Corp. (in the following called "Fitschigogerl")

Operator: Fitschigogerl Corp, represented by the Chair of the Supervisory Board Miguel Da Mota, 20 Rue Adrien-Lachenal, 1207 Geneva, Switzerland.

## Preamble:

Fitschigogerl collects, processes and uses the personal data of users in connection with the use of the services of Fitschigogerl by the user according to the following privacy policy. Below Fitschigogerl explains the extent to which data is collected, processed and used.

## 1\. Use of Data

Fitschigogerl collects personal data on the Web and on Wap-pages, or upon a user's sending SMS, MMS, or other messages in various ways in connection with the use of the products offered via the mobile networks. Fitschigogerl stores the mobile number entered by the user and the personal password for the services of Fitschigogerl. Fitschigogerl requires this information in order to provide the user with the contracted services and in order to settle via the network operator. Providing the user's consent, Fitschigogerl and its cooperation and advertising partners may send the user periodic e-mails, SMS, MMS, WAP push messages, configurations, or information about products and services which in the opinion of Fitschigogerl are of interest to the customer. The user can revoke his consent at any time for the future via e-mail to Fitschigogerl customer service: help@fitschigogerl.com Fitschigogerl uses standard encryption technology SSL (Secure Socket Layer). Under no circumstances will Fitschigogerl pass on user information to third parties except for the fulfilment of the contract, i.e.: to settle with the respective mobile company. Fitschigogerl assumes no responsibility for the processing of data on partner sites. Processing of user data as collected by Fitschigogerl is in accordance with the provisions of the Swiss Federal Act on Data Protection (DPA) and other statutory provisions (e.g.: data protection regulations of the Cantons, Civil Code (CC) and other provisions) that apply to electronic commerce. Pertaining to this, Fitschigogerl declares the following:

## 2\. No disclosure of personal data to third parties by Fitschigogerl:

There is no transfer to third parties of personal information processed by Fitschigogerl on the page www.fitschigogerl.com or of personal information processed by other mobile services.

## 3\. Non-personal data is collected automatically by Fitschigogerl:

When visiting the operated side of Fitschigogerl www.fitschigogerl.com and its sub-sites the Web server operated by Fitschigogerl on which the page www.fitschigogerl.com and the sub-sites are stored, saves the name of the user's Internet service provider, the website from which the user has called page and www.fitschigogerl.com and the (sub) pages the user visits on www.fitschigogerl.com. There is no automatic collection of any personal data on the Fitschigogerl page www.fitschigogerl.com. The date and duration of calling up Fitschigogerl are saved in an anonymous form. Fitschigogerl processes this information to determine the range of the site www.fitschigogerl.com and to optimize its offers and the services.

## 4\. Collection, processing and use of personal data by Fitschigogerl:

Personal data of the user (i.e.: mobile number and personal password) are collected by Fitschigogerl only in case the user informs Fitschigogerl of these during the course of using the offers on www.fitschigogerl.com, particularly when creating a user account on Fitschigogerl. The personal information collected from users will solely and only be used for the purpose for which the user has entered the data on the Fitschigogerl page www.fitschigogerl.com or for use and disclosure for which the user has granted permission by the user's corresponding input. This applies in particular to the use of the news service of www.fitschigogerl.com. Upon full completion of the contractual relationship - for example in case user account is deleted - the user's data must be stored according to tax and commercial retention periods; after this time, however, the data is deleted permanently unless the user has expressly agreed to further processing of the data.

Access to the data processing facilities of Fitschigogerl is always password-protected and secured against attacks from third parties at the latest state of the art level. A transfer of personal data to authorities and courts will only be executed if there is a court order or legislation forcing Fitschigogerl to do so. In this case, Fitschigogerl will limit the scope of the transmitted data is to the necessary minimum. Upon hiring, all employees of Fitschigogerl are required in writing to maintain confidentiality and to comply with data protection regulations: additionally, they are regularly reminded of their obligations and trained.

## 5\. References (links) to external websites

www.fitschigogerl.com and its sub-pages may provide links to external sites. These are of foreign content for which Fitschigogerl is not responsible under the statutory provisions, except in cases of wilful misconduct and / or gross negligence.

## 6\. Information that is automatically stored on the user's computer (cookies)

Cookies are text files that allow one to customize a Web site to the interests of the user. They take up a minimum of space and are stored by almost all operating systems and browsers in a defined position on the permanent memory of the computer of the user.

When calling up the operated side of Fitschigogerl www.fitschigogerl.com and their sub-pages information in the form of a "cookie" is temporarily or permanently stored on the user's computer. This allows the user to be recognized by the server of Fitschigogerl on his next visit to the page www.fitschigogerl.com and provide the user with individual, customized information.

In the event that the user does not wish for "cookies" to be stored with regard to the site of Fitschigogerl at www.fitschigogerl.com, the user can adjust his or her Internet browser so that it does not accept cookies and / or deletes them from the permanent memory of the computer and / or issues a warning if "cookies" are about to be placed. If in doubt, please consult the manual for your operating system and / or Internet browser.

## 7\. Processing user data through "Google Analytics":

In order to optimize the site and its marketing activities Fitschigogerl reserves the right to use "Google Analytics" by Google Inc., USA on its operated side www.fitschigogerl.com. This procedure is used to evaluate how the users use the website, to create reports on the visits to the site www.fitschigogerl.com and to (continue to) provide further services related to the use of the site. To this end, the complete IP address or a truncated IP address is processed. As necessary, Google Inc., USA will pass on the stored information to third parties, if required by law or permitted, or insofar as third parties process this data on behalf of Google Inc., United States. This analysis service of Google Inc. USA stores "Cookies" on the user's computer. The information thus obtained will be transferred to a server of Google Inc. USA and stored there. In the event that the user does not wish for "cookies" to be stored, he or she can proceed as described above (see end of sec. 5); i.e.: adjusting his or her browser setting accordingly. By accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy of Fitschigogerl on www.fitschigogerl.com the user agrees to the processing of data generated upon visiting the page www.fitschigogerl.com by the U.S. company Google Inc. for the use of Google Analytics. The user can revoke this data collection, storage and processing at any time.

In addition, the user can use the deactivation add-on by "Google Analytics"; to be found at the URL tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de. Please note, however, that this add-on is not suitable for all the Internet browsers available on the market.

## 8\. User rights regarding information, rectification, correction and deletion

Upon request of the user Fitschigogerl immediately informs the user whether and if so which personal data relating to the user are stored at Fitschigogerl. In the event that false user data are stored, these shall be rectified providing they are brought to Fitschigogerl's attention and provided they are substantiated.

In addition, the user has the right to have personal data collected by Fitschigogerl on the page www.fitschigogerl.com blocked and/or deleted. Fitschigogerl uses the user data to inform the user about the services of Fitschigogerl. To do so, the consent of the user is required. If the user wishes to revoke this agreement, he or she may do so in writing any time. We are happy to answer any further questions on data protection at Fitschigogerl at any time. Please refer to our imprint for contact details.

Geneva, September 2011

Fitschigogerl Corp.
